// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the current archons is the oldest?",
    answer: "Morax",
    options: [
      "Buer",
      "Beelzbul",
      "Morax",
      "Barbatos"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Who runs the Wangsheng Funeral Parlour?",
    answer: "Hu Tao",
    options: [
      "Zhongli",
      "Hu Tao",
      "Ningguang",
      "Baizhu"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What martial arts group is Xingqiu in?",
    answer: "Guhua Clan",
    options: [
      "Guhua Clan",
      "Guhra Clan",
      "Guava Clan",
      "Guha Clan"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which character was on the first limited banner?",
    answer: "Venti",
    options: [
      "Klee",
      "Zhongli",
      "Venti",
      "Tartaglia"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of these characters ISN'T obtained for free?",
    answer: "Razor",
    options: [
      "Kaeya",
      "Barbara",
      "Xiangling",
      "Razor"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which character's specialty food is a fried egg?",
    answer: "Bennett",
    options: [
      "Rosaria",
      "Qiqi",
      "Venti",
      "Bennett"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of these areas ISN'T in Mondstadt?",
    answer: "Sea of Clouds",
    options: [
      "Cape oath",
      "Musk Reef",
      "Sea of Clouds",
      "Dragonspine"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "How many weapon types are there?",
    answer: "5",
    options: [
      "4",
      "5",
      "6",
      "7"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Who is the Yuheng of the Liyue Qixing?",
    answer: "Keqing",
    options: [
      "Keqing",
      "Ningguang",
      "Ganyu",
      "Yelan"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "When does the spiral abyss reset?",
    answer: "Every two weeks",
    options: [
      "Every month",
      "Every week",
      "Every two weeks",
      "Every three weeks"
    ]
  }
    
];